はい。
今日は
コブクロのカバンの中身
なんかだんだん
このYouTubeも慣れてきたね。
そうですね。
慣れてきたね？
ね？
楽しくなってきたね。
僕もこれから職業欄には
もう入れてる、入れ、
それ言うと
ほんまにWikipediaに書かれんねんから。
YouTuberで。
俺はもうYouTuberやで。
まあ、やってる時点で。
そうすね。
今日はえと
カバンの中身って言うやつ
これはよくね、テレビとかでやりますよね。
Right?
Who would have thought that the day we'd do such a thing would come?
Honestly though,
we did have this conversation about
please do "Inside the Bag"
a TV show offered us to do.
(?) Since we didn't have spare time, we said no.
Until now we said "no" about 100 times.
(?) Why because of spare time?
This story, this story. right?
People that think of YouTube, you know
when they asked us "How about next time?"
The time we said "ok"
the staff was so surprised.
Even though before we refused that much.
Right.
Kuroda's bar for YouTube,
is very low.
That's how serious I am about YouTube.
This is ok.
Ok, then
Kobuchi
Is it ok to show something realistic?
This is the bag I always carry.
Kobuchi bag.
Hey, Kuroda,
can you quickly carry this with one hand?
With one hand.
Hold it quickly.
Hey, my back is going to get messed up.
Well, I use this everyday.
Kobuchi is actually
as is, right?
There's a lot of stuff.
Ok, this is obvious.
My computer.
Lyrics, memos, everything, songs.
We can't show the desktop computer, but
to the point where you don't know which one is which,
there's like 100 icons on there.
Right, there's an enormous amount.
It is messy.
Ah, well
Computer charger.
Charge.
This is,
You have this.
Yes, yes.
Well recently,
I have bought a camera.
What kind of camera did you buy?
This is amazing.
Um,
Even in this compact digital camera,
this Canon, G5X
So Kobuchi's, you see
that
Kobuchi's
This even comes with a tripod.
That's amazing.
It doesn't come with it.
I added it.
Oh you added it.
That's amazing.
(?) I devised this.
No matter what, you,
after a month, you'll stop using this thing.
You sure are annoying.
Anyways
Masks, right?
A mask case?
Yup.
I always put a mask case in here.
That and also
It's obvious, but
さくいんばこ？？？
I put in a wallet.
The wallet is already
this is Matsukata Hiroki's thing, huh?
It was already
No, no. no.
I won't, I won't open it, but
What is this...?
This is frightening.
I'm scared.
I'm scared to open it.
I won't open it!
I won't open it! But anyways,
It's kinda incredible.
No, no.
This is what they are,
these things called long wallets.
No, no, no.
And then,
tea, right?
Hey, come on...
Hey, this, well
Takahashi Mary June drinks the same thing.
??? Hey, don't make fun of "Azuki Beautiful Women Tea"!
How long do you think I've been drinking this?
The thing you drink
is the same thing models drink.
Oh.
Why do you always have these kinds of things in there?
Isn't it normal?
I'm getting a bit nervous.
The thing you rub your face with might appear.
It won't appear, it won't appear.
Anyways, the rest is, well
I put things in like sunglasses, and
I put in accessories I wear at places, right?
You're fast, huh?
This, everyone
I put in a little perfume.
Um, no.
In a bottle?
(?) Not separately?
With a bottle.
With a bottle??
You bring it in a bottle?!
That's sure is amazing.
With a bottle.
That is amazing.
Because I have this, see?
It's secure.
This thing that closes like this.
Can this pass their airport?
Um,
There are times when I put it in a large one, but
(?) You can't tell regardless of whether it's big or small.
The rest is, well,
things like a charging adapter,
another one.
This, um, what's it called?
Ear phones.
Oh, this.
This!
This is extremely useful.
From one USB port,
USB-C, Lightning...
Um.
There's everything on this.
Because there are four prongs.
I have a small version of that.
(?) Is that so?
Today, this is what I intended to boast about the most,
so I brought it.
So with mine,
here, at the opening,
you can replace it with any of the three.
So with this,
with 4,
you can charge 4 at a time?
That's right.
That's why,
the speed is 1/4.
That's unacceptable.
But, it can do 4 at a time?
Yes, yes, yes.
So if I have a lot time to spare,
I use this.
When he has time to spare...
Ah! And this is,
a mobile air purifier.
It appeared...
Huh?
Why, everyone wears this.
This, Takahashi Mary June also has the same thing.
In principle, um,
in one minute,
the purified air is,
the air only around this is purified.
You know...
My surroundings are
Hey, stop that.
You're going to stop using that,
pretty soon.
Inside, there's a small purple light.
Everyone probably thinks this is a joke.
This is the reality.
This guy always has things like that in his bag.
The rest is,
now I'm doing things like writing some lyrics.
And books I want to read, right?
But they're in your computer.
No, no.
The thing about books is,
if it's not a book, I can't.
These kinds of books I really like.
(?) Things like "searching for words"
This is amazing.
This is a bit of that, right?
Kobuchi.
You just added these to look cool.
No, no, no!
I actually put these in.
You totally added these to your bag just for coolness, didn't you?
In your bag?
A little bit for coolness right?
A little...
I'm writing a little lyrics,
I wanted to show these, right?
Because, this is almost
unused.
It feels like it was never opened, right?
Stop it.
Today is a YouTube recording,
so I brought them.
The next is, well,
headphones.
Yes, this is, you know,
Hey, you know,
You already have earphones,
why do you need headphones?
This is what Neumann released.
Oh, is it?
Neumann released this.
Wow.
This, recently I've been using this very much.
This.
(?) Super topic.
Right?
Well even afterwards,
it's like that.
Ah, the next is, well,
earphones, right?
How many earphones do you have?
You have 3 that seem the same though.
No.
A weird person who use these while on the move.
If on the move, I use these.
When do you use this?
This?
This is when I run, for example.
Ah,
there's already 3 in here.
One is enough,
just one.
Well the rest is, already,
that right?
Cough drops I always suck on.
Chapstick, right?
And next,
throat spray.
Something like Cemedine.
This is for your nose.
For pollen, those things you wear on your nose.
???
A little supplements, for example.
That's that.
???
is the most
(?) the clatter of the main topic of today, right?
You didn't bring but,
(?) The clatter, this
about 4 times the amount here, right?
Already, about the amount of one person living alone.
Like the same.
Yes.
Let's spread this all out.
Yes. Oh these? Everything.
Kobuchi's stuff.
I'm so good at lining these up.
Like lining stuff up, or
when writing on the blackboard
you're really good at, but,
the inside of your bag is extremely messy.
Why? I wonder.
You ask, but,
how do I clean up the inside of my bag?
How?
This is a different skill, right?
How do I clean the inside of my bag?
Because, there are no divisions.
So, I'll say one thing.
You don't need all this.
No... I need it.
Computer, and,
this charger, and
wallet,
and then
you only need one, either earphones or headphones.
I don't like that...
You also don't need a camera anymore.
なんて???しいな
Not needed.
I need it, I need it.
I definitely need this.
Yes.
But this is actually,
my,
a bit.
But really,
this is it.
Yes.
This was the inside of my bag.
Next time.
I always bring this around.
Actually,
this is the first time I-
(?)いごえる Boku-note
Inside Kobukuro Kuroda's bag.