Yes.
Today is
The inside of Kobukuro's bag.
We've gotten more
used to this YouTube thing.
Right?
We got used to it right?
It became fun.
From now on, I'm putting in the "occupation" field
You're already putting it in.
When you say that
then it's actually going to be written on Wikipedia.
As a YouTuber
I'm already a YouTuber.
Well, at this time as we are doing it.
Right, right.
So, today
so the thing called "Inside the Bag"
is often shown on TV, right?
Right?
Who would have thought that the day we'd do such a thing would come?
Honestly though,
we did have this conversation about
please do "Inside the Bag"
a TV show offered us to do.
(?) Since we didn't have spare time, we said no.
Until now we said "no" about 100 times.
(?) Why because of spare time?
This story, this story. right?
People that think of YouTube, you know
when they asked us "How about next time?"
The time we said "ok"
the staff was so surprised.
Even though before we refused that much.
Right.
Kuroda's bar for YouTube,
is very low.
That's how serious I am about YouTube.
This is ok.
Ok, then