Thank you very much!
We had you listen to "Sakura", "Wind", and "The Flower that Only Grows Here".
Thank you.
I have, um, a hometown called Miyazaki.
Even now, um,
I gather with my related uncles and aunts.
Or, as it is called,
like a hometown gathering,
we remove the sliding door of our house and there is a place where we have everyone gather together.
And over there,
when I go there every year,
I think of things like "I changed a little",
or like "I'm thinking of such excessive things".
I realized that, whenever I'm there, I can capture all of these thoughts.
We only have normal conversations,
and every year, we have the same food,
no matter how many years later, it's the same.
Roll sushi, and
the same sashimi, and
the same chicken dishes appear.
Nothing changes, but,
Because of that, I can notice that I've changed.
It's like,
it's very...
I thought of it like that, and thought "oh, right."
If you go far from your hometown that much,
you cover yourself with the part of you that isn't you,
and that part ends up walking ahead.
And there are times where you feel like you want to surpass that part.
"So there are times like that", I thought.
So to me, the part of my hometown that I imagined,
the song called "The Flower that Only Grows Here",
is very big.
But whenever I talk about my hometown story to Kuroda,
like about removing the sliding door and relatives gathering, or
when I was little, I would stay over the whole time,
the same kid that was 5 years, 10 years old,
even when the kid becomes an adult, the fact that we are together even now,
is unbelieveable in a way. From the time he partnered with me,
I continuously told him this,
it was those gatherings, I would say, but
he didn't have much of a thing like a family gathering.
For a long time, he's been saying this.
And so,
I wonder,
in a town called Osaka,
where Kuroda was born, then left Sakai,